all right hello and welcome I'm Pooh
好的，你好，欢迎光临，我是维尼
number half I'm working in JVM
我在JVM中工作的人数占一半
sustaining engineering team at Oracle a
甲骨文公司的可持续工程团队
gentleman here asked you know what does
绅士在这里问你知道什么
JVM sustaining engineer it's an
JVM维护工程师
interesting title
有趣的标题
interesting title so JVM sustaining
有趣的标题，使JVM得以维持
engineering as a group in Oracle where
在Oracle中作为一个团队进行工程设计
we work really hard on resolving
我们非常努力地解决
customer escalated problems against
客户针对的问题升级
hotspot JVM so here's a little bit about
热点JVM，所以这里有一些关于
me I'm a co-author of the book Java
我是Java一书的合著者
performance companion I have been
我去过的表演伙伴
speaking at Java one for a couple of
在Java上讲了两次
years and a Java one rockstar I've been
多年，我去过Java的摇滚明星
speaking at other Java conferences as
在其他Java大会上发言
well I maintain a blog here at this link
好吧，我在此链接上维护一个博客
and I published a number of articles on
我发表了许多关于
how to troubleshoot problems in hotspot
如何解决热点问题
JVM so all right how many of you have
JVM，好的，你们有多少人
seen this out of memory error exception
看到此内存不足错误异常
everybody ok so so you are in the right
大家还好，所以你在对的地方
room so whenever we see this exception
房间，所以只要我们看到此异常
you know we are kind of scared oh this
你知道我们有点害怕哦
means that there is some sort of memory
意味着有某种记忆
related issue with my application and
与我的应用程序相关的问题
I'll have to spend days and nights
我将不得不日日夜夜
figuring out what's wrong with my
找出我的问题是什么
application you know why this exception
应用程序，您知道为什么会出现此异常
is occurring so this is kind of a
正在发生，所以这有点
symptom that there is something related
有相关的症状
to memory which is you know which is
记住那是你的记忆
which is not right with the application
这与应用程序不正确
so not just out of memory error
所以不仅仅是内存不足错误
exception there are other symptoms such
例外还有其他症状
as unexpected memory growth in our
由于我们的内存意外增长
application or poor application
应用或不良应用
performance which kind of indicate that
性能表明
our application is struggling with
我们的应用程序正在努力
memory issues and we should be
内存问题，我们应该
investigating that and oftentimes these
调查，并经常这些
symptoms are connected to GC activities
症状与GC活动有关
in Java applications from
在Java应用程序中
and those you know can be conformed by
而你所知道的可以通过
looking at GC logs or monitoring our
查看GC日志或监视我们的
applications and conforming that there
应用程序并在那里进行验证
are are there long GC pauses are their
是否有长时间的GC暂停是他们的
excessive GCS and my application which
过多的GCS和我的申请
could be caused due to miss
可能是由于错过
configuration of memory pools excessive
内存池配置过多
use of finalized errs explicit GC
使用最终错误的显式GC
invocations or even a memory leak in the
调用甚至内存泄漏
application so in this session our goal
应用程序，因此在本节中我们的目标
is to understand how we can go about
是了解我们如何去做
from symptoms or behavior those specific
从特定的症状或行为
behaviors and our application to the
行为及其对我们的应用
bottom box what is causing those
底盒是什么原因造成的
symptoms in our application this is what
我们的应用程序中的症状是什么
the agenda looks like we'll be talking
议程看起来就像我们要谈论的
about memory issues related to Java he
关于与Java有关的内存问题
permanent generation meta space code
永久生成元空间代码
cache native memory and what you know
缓存本机内存和您所知道的
what is causing those issues and how do
是什么导致了这些问题，以及如何做
we troubleshoot them we'll also take a
我们对它们进行故障排除，我们还将采取
look at out of memory related issues due
查看与内存不足相关的问题
to finalization so Java heap memory
最终确定，以便Java堆内存
issues so when we when we look at those
问题，当我们看着那些
symptoms you know just rather rather
你知道的症状相当
than just jumping at the conclusion that
而不是仅仅得出结论
all my application is having a memory
我所有的应用程序都有内存
leak because I see those symptoms there
泄漏，因为我在那里看到那些症状
is unexpected memory growth there is
出现意外的内存增长
poor poor performance of the application
糟糕的应用程序性能
or my application is failing with out of
或我的应用失败
memory error before doing that before
之前做的内存错误
jumping at the conclusion that there is
得出结论认为
a memory leak we first should confirm
我们首先应该确认内存泄漏
whether there is a memory leak we should
是否有内存泄漏，我们应该
monitor our Java heap usage over time if
随时间监视我们的Java堆使用情况
there are full G C's occurring during
在此期间发生了完整的G C
the runtime of our application
应用程序的运行时
are those fuji c's able to claim reclaim
那些富士C能够要求回收
space in the old generation of the Java
Java的老一代中的空间
heap if they are not then probably it's
如果不是，那就堆
just a configuration issue our Java heap
只是配置问题，我们的Java堆
size may not be appropriately configured
尺寸可能未正确配置
it might be sized too small so the first
它的大小可能太小，因此第一个
step is increase the heap size test the
步骤是增加堆大小测试
application again and if there is still
再次申请，如果还有
can take continuous memory growth in the
可以使
application in our processes then
然后在我们的流程中应用
probably you know there is a likelihood
也许你知道有可能
that there is a memory leak in the
在内存泄漏
application so we can use various tools
应用程序，因此我们可以使用各种工具
to monitor heap usage of our application
监视应用程序的堆使用情况
for example in this case this is J
例如，在这种情况下，这是J
console connected to a live application
控制台连接到实时应用程序
and monitoring the heap usage in this
并在此监视堆使用情况
case it is clear that permanent
情况很明显，永久
generation occupancy is growing over
代住人数正在增长
time if it is not possible to do life
时间，如果不可能做生活
monitoring of the application we can
我们可以监控应用程序
collect GC logs and we can analyze those
收集GC日志，我们可以对其进行分析
those GC logs to see what is the heap
这些GC日志以查看堆是什么
usage of our application you know is it
您知道我们应用程序的用途吗
is it sized appropriately is it good
尺寸合适吗？
enough is it big enough to hold the live
足够大吗？
data set of our application for example
例如我们的应用程序的数据集
in this case from the GC log you can see
在这种情况下，您可以从GC日志中看到
that even after full GCS the heap usage
即使在完全GCS之后，堆使用情况
is continuously growing so the option we
持续增长，所以我们选择
should be using to appropriately sized
应该使用适当的大小
our Java heap is - X MX which sets the
我们的Java堆是-X MX，它设置了
maximum heap size for our Java heap and
Java堆的最大堆大小，以及
we recommend setting this value equal to
我们建议将此值设置为等于
the value of minus X ms which sets the
负X ms的值，用于设置
initial value of Java heap so so there
Java堆的初始值，所以在那里
are three steps of troubleshooting any
是排除任何故障的三个步骤
problem you know understand that what
你知道的问题明白什么
the problem is for example in this case
问题是在这种情况下
we are looking at out of memory or
我们正在看内存不足或
memory related issues to Java heap
Java堆的内存相关问题
second step is to get insights into the
第二步是深入了解
problem to collect diagnostic data from
从中收集诊断数据的问题
the system and the third step is to
系统，第三步是
analyze that data to understand why the
分析该数据以了解为什么
problem is occurring and find the
问题发生了，找到
solution so let's go ahead with the step
解决方案，所以让我们继续下一步
of collecting diagnostic data what
诊断数据的收集
diagnostic data we should be collecting
我们应该收集的诊断数据
to to troubleshoot Java heap related
解决与Java堆相关的问题
memory problem
记忆问题
and so far for for Java heap related
到目前为止，与Java堆相关
memory issues we should be collecting GC
我们应该收集GC的内存问题
logs heap dump heap histograms so let's
记录堆转储堆直方图，所以让我们
take a look at you know in detail one by
看一看你所知道的详细
one how we which tools we can use to
一个我们如何使用哪些工具
collect this data and how this each each
收集这些数据以及每个数据如何
each diagnostic data helps us in
每个诊断数据都可以帮助我们
troubleshooting GC locks they are very
故障排除GC锁，它们非常
helpful in determining the heap
有助于确定堆
requirements they tell us what is the
要求他们告诉我们什么是
you know the appropriate size of Java
你知道合适的Java大小
heap
堆
they tell us if there are excessive GCS
他们告诉我们是否有过多的GCS
or if there are long GC pauses in
或者如果有很长的GC暂停
application execution these are the GC
应用程序执行这些是GC
logging options that can be used to
日志记录选项，可用于
collect GC logs for Java 9 we can we use
收集我们可以使用的Java 9的GC日志
my new JVM option minus X log GC to
我的新JVM选项减去X log GC即可
collect GC logs and you know these these
收集GC日志，您知道这些
in the first two lines tell us the GC
前两行告诉我们GC
log options to be used with G 1 and non
G 1和非1使用的日志选项
G 1 collectors and for prior Java
G 1收集器和以前的Java
versions we can use print GC details
我们可以使用打印GC详细信息的版本
print GC time stamps date stamps and
打印GC时间戳，日期戳和
minus X log GC these options are not
减X log GC，这些选项不是
available in Jellico 9 they have been
在Jellico 9中可用，他们已经
you know you would see a warning that
你知道你会看到一个警告
these are deprecated but internally they
这些已过时，但内部
are mapped to using minus X log option
使用减X日志选项映射到
so here in this example we can see that
所以在这个例子中我们可以看到
from GC logs we can see heap usage in
从GC日志中，我们可以看到堆使用情况
this example there is a full GC and it
这个例子有一个完整的GC，它
is not able to collect any spare any any
无法收集任何备用
you know it is not able to free up any
你知道它无法释放任何
space in all generation which means that
世代相传的空间
probably old generation is not big
大概老一代不大
enough to hold data or hold the live
足以保存数据或保存实时数据
data set of our application GC logs also
我们的应用程序GC日志的数据集
can show us if there are excessive G C's
可以告诉我们是否有过多的G C
in this case there are back-to-back
在这种情况下，背靠背
frequent full GC s which you know impact
您知道影响的频繁完整GC
the application performance very badly
应用程序性能很差
GC rocks can show us if there are long
GC岩石可以告诉我们是否有很长的时间
GC pauses
GC暂停
this case there's a full GC which is
在这种情况下，有一个完整的GC
taking 50 seconds of time and that's
花费50秒的时间
pretty long so we should investigate and
很长一段时间，所以我们应该调查并
find out why these long cc's are
找出为什么这些长抄送是
occurring and how we can avoid full G
发生以及如何避免全G
season our application so the next
调味我们的应用程序，以便下一个
diagnostic data which is the most
诊断数据最多
important diagnostic data to
重要的诊断数据
troubleshoot memory related issues is
解决与内存相关的问题是
heap dumps it can be collected using J
可以使用J收集堆转储
command J map J console Java mission
命令J map J控制台Java任务
control and also there is an option he
控制，还有一个选择，他
pump on out of memory error which is you
泵出内存不足错误是你
know pretty handy because you have this
知道很方便，因为你有这个
in place when you launch your java
在启动Java时就位
applications and if in case your
申请，如果您的
application fails with out of memory
应用程序失败，内存不足
error you would have heap dump available
错误，您将有可用的堆转储
with you to to to troubleshoot later on
和您一起来解决问题
you know why your application failed
你知道为什么你的申请失败了
with out of memory error so in this
有内存不足错误，所以在此
snapshot I hope you can see clearly at
快照，希望您能清楚看到
the back so this is J console showing
后面，这是J控制台显示
that there are n beans in this case hot
在这种情况下有n个豆子很热
spot diagnostic M bean and it has an
现场诊断M Bean，它具有
operation dump heap using that operation
使用该操作的操作转储堆
we can collect heap dumps from live
我们可以从现场收集堆转储
running applications so this screenshot
运行应用程序，因此此屏幕截图
shows Java Mission Control through Java
通过Java显示Java任务控制
Mission Control as well it is possible
任务控制也是可能的
to collect heap dump again there are two
再次收集堆转储有两个
am beans a hot spot diagnostic and
是豆类热点诊断和
diagnostic command using their
使用他们的诊断命令
operations in this case dump heap
在这种情况下的操作转储堆
operation of hot hot spot diagnostic and
热点诊断操作和
bean we can collect heap dumps so as I
豆，我们可以收集堆转储，所以我
mentioned there is a JVM option heap
提到有一个JVM选项堆
dump on out of memory error which can be
转储出内存错误，可能是
used to collect heap dumps in case there
用于收集堆转储，以防在那里
is a JVM fails with out of memory error
是JVM失败并显示内存不足错误
so here we can see that you know on the
所以在这里我们可以看到您知道
on the left hand side from the GC logs
在GC日志的左侧
we can see that the application is
我们可以看到该应用程序是
failing with GC overhead
出现GC开销失败
limit exceeded out of memory error and
超出内存限制错误，并且
after that there it is it is creating
在那之后，它正在创造
the heap dump so there are scenarios
堆转储，所以有方案
where you know especially parallel
你知道特别平行的地方
collector it can continuously put in its
收集器可以连续放入
efforts to collect you know or reclaim
努力收集您知道或回收的
some space and the in in Java heap even
Java堆中甚至还有一些空间
though the returns of that are very
虽然那的回报非常
minimal so in such cases you know we
最小，所以在这种情况下，您知道我们
have to instruct the garbage collector
必须指示垃圾收集器
that don't you know don't put in so many
你不知道不要投入那么多
so much effort when the gains are are
当收获是
not significant you should exit come out
不重要，你应该退出出来
of it and you know let the application
它，你知道让应用程序
stop or let the if there is a if there
停下或让如果有的话
is a you know application server hosted
是托管的应用服务器吗
application let it restart on its own so
应用程序让它自己重启
in such scenarios it can actually delay
在这种情况下，它实际上可能会延迟
the exit or restart of the application
退出或重新启动应用程序
and it delays the creation of heap dump
并且延迟了堆转储的创建
as well so so this delay can actually
以及这样的延迟实际上可以
have performance penalties for our
对我们的性能有影响
application so first for such scenarios
首先针对此类情况
we can use two JVM options GC time limit
我们可以使用两个JVM选项GC时间限制
and GC heap free limit so GC time limit
和GC堆可用限制，因此GC时间限制
sets an upper limit on the amount of
设置数量上限
time that GCS can spend in percent of
GCS可以花费的时间百分比
total time and GC heap free limit Setser
总时间和GC堆可用限制设置程序
lower limit on the amount of space that
下限的空间
should be free after garbage collections
垃圾收集后应该免费
so the default value of GC time limit is
因此GC时间限制的默认值为
98 percent on the default value of GC
GC默认值的98％
heap free limit is two percent which
堆可用限制为百分之二
means if the garbage collections are
意味着如果垃圾收集是
able to meet these two conditions it can
能够满足这两个条件
you know the garbage collections are
你知道垃圾收集是
allowed to take up to 98 percent of the
允许占用高达98％的
time and if there is at least two
时间，如果至少有两个
percent of the heap space free after
之后的可用堆空间百分比
collections the garbage collections will
垃圾收集将
continue they they won't exit you know
继续他们他们不会退出你知道的
there will be back-to-back frequent full
将会有频繁的背靠背
GCS so we can tune these two options we
GCS，因此我们可以调整这两个选项
can try to in
可以尝试
Cree's GC time limit and we can try to
Cree的GC时间限制，我们可以尝试
increase GC heap a free limit so that we
增加GC堆的可用限制，以便我们
don't have this this issue of
没有这个问题
back-to-back frequent full G C's in
背靠背频繁的完整G C
cases where the applique expect the
贴花期望的情况
application to to exit rather than
申请退出而不是退出
lingering around there so an out of
徘徊在那里，所以
memory error is thrown after a full GC
完整的GC后引发内存错误
if the previous five consecutive GCS are
如果前五个连续的GCS是
not able to meet the the value set by
无法达到设定的值
these two JVM options so the next
这两个JVM选项，所以接下来
diagnostic data is heap histogram he
诊断数据是堆直方图
pistol Graham's give quick glimpse of
格雷厄姆手枪快速浏览
objects in Java heap so you don't have
Java堆中的对象，因此您没有
you don't have to follow two steps you
您不必遵循两个步骤
know collect heap dumps and then analyze
知道收集堆转储，然后分析
them using some tool so these are
他们使用一些工具，所以这些是
textual you know output where you can
你知道的文本输出在哪里可以
quickly see which objects are which kind
快速查看哪些对象是哪种
of objects are growing in heap heap now
堆中的对象数量正在增长
this heap histograms can be collected
可以收集此堆直方图
using the print class histogram J
使用印刷类直方图J
command J map and there is a new tool J
命令J地图，并且有一个新工具J
HSD be added in jdk 9 which can be used
将HSD添加到可以使用的jdk 9中
to collect heap dumps from code files or
从代码文件收集堆转储或
nonresponsive processes as well and we
以及无响应的流程，我们
can use diagnostic commands in Java
可以在Java中使用诊断命令
Mission Control to collect heap
任务控制收集堆
histograms let's see some examples here
直方图让我们在这里看一些例子
we can see Java Mission Control in that
我们可以在其中看到Java Mission Control
we can execute GC dot class histogram
我们可以执行GC点类直方图
operation
运作
you know diagnostic command on the live
你知道实时诊断命令
process to collect heap histogram and it
收集堆直方图的过程及其
shows the heap histogram at the bottom
在底部显示堆直方图
pane of Java Mission Control so once we
Java Mission Control的窗格，所以一旦我们
have collected data we have GC logs we
收集了数据，我们有GC日志，
have heap terms we have histograms which
有堆条件，我们有直方图
tools should be used to analyze that
应该使用工具来分析
data to see you know what what kind of
数据看你知道什么样的
memory problem I'm encountering GC log
我遇到GC日志的内存问题
and GC logs analysis so in the GC logs
和GC日志分析，因此在GC日志中
what do we want to look for we want to
我们想要寻找什么我们想要
see if there are too many Fuji sees if
看富士是否看得太多
are those G sees
是那些G看到的
having long pauses are those eces
那些停顿很长的时间
occurring too frequently we can do
发生得太频繁，我们可以做
manual inspection of the GC logs are
手动检查GC日志是
there are automatic analysis tools
有自动分析工具
available which we can use to you know
我们可以使用的可用信息
understand what what's what's happening
了解发生了什么事
what's wrong with my memory
我的记忆怎么了
configuration are why these GCS are
配置就是为什么这些GCS
occurring too frequently or why they are
发生得太频繁或为什么
taking too much time so here this is a
花费太多时间，所以这是一个
GC viewer tool in this week if we look
如果我们看本周的GC查看器工具
closely there are GC pause you know to
紧密地有GC暂停，您知道
space exhausted events there are two
空间耗尽事件有两个
collections which are full GCS and they
完整的GCS集合
took around four seconds each you know
每个人大概花了四秒钟
not each they took in total they took
不是每个人总花费了
around four seconds which is you know a
大约四秒钟，你知道吗
long pause for for response and
长时间的等待响应和
intensive intensive applications so in
密集应用
such cases you know this is a this is a
这样的情况，你知道这是一个这是一个
GC log of G one collector and two space
G个收集器和两个空间的GC日志
exhausted GC me DC's mean that there is
用尽GC me DC的意思是
not enough room available in the old
旧空间不足
regions to promote objects from the
促进对象从
young regions so inside it's in such
年轻的地区，所以里面就是这样
scenarios we have to make sure you know
场景，我们必须确保您知道
our old region's old generation and
我们旧地区的老一代
young generation are sized appropriately
调整年轻一代的大小
there is enough room available in the
有足够的空间
old generation and in g1 there are mixed
老一辈，在g1中混合在一起
collections
馆藏
you know the collections in which some
你知道其中一些收藏
of the old regions are collected along
的旧区域是沿着
with young regions so we have to make
与年轻的地区，所以我们必须
sure those mixed GCS are running
确保那些混合的GCS正在运行
effectively
有效
if we look closely there is an option
如果我们仔细观察，有一个选择
you know there is at the bottom we can
你知道我们可以在底部
see that initiating occupancy fraction
看到初始占用率
which is a value that indicates at which
这是一个值，该值指示
fraction the concurrent marking cycle of
分数的同时标记周期
g1 collector should start which prepares
g1收集器应该开始进行准备
the old generation regions
老一代地区
so that they can be included in mixed
这样就可以将它们混合在一起
regions
地区
you know if the mixed collections are
你知道混合收藏是否
not not having old generation regions as
没有旧的地区作为
part of them the old data doesn't get
其中一部分旧数据无法获取
collected the only objects that have
收集了唯一具有
been renewed that have been moved to all
更新了，已经转移到所有人
generation don't get collected so here
一代人没有被收集，所以这里
we can see that the this occupancy
我们可以看到这个占用
fraction is set at as 87 percent if we
如果我们将分数设置为87％
reduce this percentage we would you know
减少这个百分比，你会知道吗
start the the concurrent marking cycle
开始并发标记周期
of g1 collector earlier which would
较早的g1收集器
which would make sure that the old
这将确保旧的
regions are ready for mixed collections
地区准备好进行混合收集
and would leave enough room in the older
并会留出足够的空间
generation for promotion of promotions
代促销活动
of objects from young regions so next
来自年轻地区的物品，所以接下来
thing to look for is do we have explicit
要寻找的是我们是否明确
Fuji sees because explicit Fuji sees can
富士看到，因为明确的富士看到可以
cause long pauses in our application and
导致我们的应用程序长时间停顿，并且
they are easy to spot in the GC logs if
如果很容易在GC日志中发现它们
you look for a system strength in the GC
您在GC中寻找系统优势
log entries that means that there are
日志条目，这意味着有
explicit full GC is being invoked these
显式完整GC正在调用这些
explicit full GC s can be invoked using
显式完整GC可以使用调用
system dot GC call if you are using RM I
系统点GC调用（如果使用的是RM I）
and you know the RM I applications at
并且您知道RM I应用程序位于
certain intervals which is specified
指定的特定间隔
with these properties invoke explicit
这些属性调用显式
full GCS and if we need to we need to
完整的GCS，如果需要，我们需要
make sure that the diagnostic tools we
确保我们使用的诊断工具
are using to collect the diagnostic data
正在用于收集诊断数据
they are not you know unknowingly they
他们不是你不知不觉中他们
are not invoking full GCS in our
没有在我们的系统中调用完整的GCS
application for example if we have
例如，如果我们有
option print class histogram in our
我们的选项打印类直方图
application enabled and if we send sick
启用了应用程序，如果我们生病了
break or secret signal to the
中断或秘密信号
application it would invoke a full GC
应用程序，它将调用完整的GC
before collecting the class histogram or
在收集班级直方图之前或
the object histogram so in such
对象直方图
scenarios we have to be aware
我们必须注意的场景
that we our application doesn't have
我们的应用程序没有
explicit full GCS getting invoked there
显式完整GCS在那里被调用
is an option disable explicit GC which
是一个选项，禁用显式GC
can you know completely disable the the
你知道完全禁用
explicit GC invocation for our
我们的显式GC调用
applications so once we have heap dumps
应用程序，所以一旦我们有了堆转储
collected how do we analyze heap dumps
收集了我们如何分析堆转储
there are you know plenty of tools
你知道很多工具
available for heap dump analysis until
可用于堆转储分析，直到
JDK 8 we had J ha Java visual VM which
在JDK 8中，我们拥有了Java虚拟机J ha
have been removed from JDK 9 but you
已从JDK 9中删除，但是您
know the open source project of Java
知道Java的开源项目
visual VM is still available if you if
如果以下情况，可视VM仍然可用
you wish to run your JDK 9 applications
您希望运行JDK 9应用程序
you know if you wish to analyze heap
你知道你是否想分析堆
dumps from your JDK 9 applications you
从您的JDK 9应用程序转储
can you could still use Java visual vm
你还能使用Java visual vm吗
and there is an excellent tool eclipse
而且有一个很好的日食
mat which is a community developed
社区开发的垫子
open-source tool and it has you know
开源工具，它知道
amazing features which lets you explore
惊人的功能，让您探索
dig deep into your heap dumps and see
深入研究堆堆，看看
what might be consuming memory in your
什么可能会消耗您的内存
heaps so here I have a heap dump open an
堆所以在这里我有一个堆转储打开
eclipse mat in this case we can see that
在这种情况下，我们可以看到
the instances of byte array are taking
字节数组的实例正在
up to four hundred and six megabytes and
高达460兆字节
we can in Eclipse matte we can go and
我们可以在Eclipse遮罩中去
look at the instance instances of this
看一下这个的实例
byte array and here we can see a pattern
字节数组，在这里我们可以看到一个模式
that you know byte array of length one
你知道长度为一的字节数组
zero two four are repeating there there
零二四在那儿重复
are too many objects of one zero two
一零二的对象太多
four length byte array in eclipse mat we
eclipse mat中的四个长度的字节数组
can see the reference chains of these
可以看到这些参考链
objects to their GC roots which means
反对他们的GC根
the roots in the JVM which are holding
JVM中的根
on to these objects and which are not
在这些对象上，哪些不是
letting them be collected by the garbage
让他们被垃圾收集
collector so in this case we can see
收集器，所以在这种情况下，我们可以看到
that there is a vector long-lived object
有一个向量寿命长的物体
in memory Li class which is actually
在记忆里的李课，实际上
responsible for holding on to this these
负责坚持这些
byte array instances
字节数组实例
so permanent generation metaphase memory
所以永久世代中期记忆
issues so in this case as well like we
问题，在这种情况下，就像我们一样
did in Java heap with Java heap memory
用Java堆内存在Java堆中完成
related issues in this case also we need
在这种情况下，我们也需要相关的问题
to first confirm if there is a memory
首先确认是否有记忆
leak monitored your permanent generation
泄漏监控您的永久一代
or meta space usage over time and if
或随着时间推移的元空间使用情况，以及
full G C's are not able to claim any
完整的G C无法声明任何
space from meta space or form John that
从元空间或约翰形成的空间
could mean that your permanent
可能意味着你的永久
generation or meta space is not sized
世代或元空间的大小不正确
appropriately increase the size test
适当增加尺寸测试
your application again and if it stills
您的应用程序再次，如果仍然
you know after the application reaches a
您知道申请到达后
steady state if it still keeps growing
如果它仍然保持稳定状态
in size its its occupancy still keeps
在规模上它的占有率仍然保持
growing that would indicate that
增长表明
probably there is a memory leak to
可能有内存泄漏
configure it is native but it is
配置它是本地的，但是它是
collected by the garbage collector so
因此被垃圾收集器收集
configure to configure our permanent
配置以配置我们的永久
generation we can use two options
一代我们可以使用两种选择
permanent generation
永久的一代
palm size and Max palm size to set the
手掌大小和最大手掌大小来设置
initial and the maximum permanent
初始和最大永久
generation size a point to note here is
代大小这里要注意的一点是
that permanent generation has been
那永久的一代已经
removed in JDK 8 so we don't have how
已在JDK 8中删除，因此我们没有
many generations JDK 8 onwards there is
从JDK 8开始，有很多代
meta space where we store class metadata
我们存储类元数据的元空间
information so to configure meta space
信息，以便配置元空间
meta space size and max meta space size
元空间大小和最大元空间大小
JVM options if max meta space size is
JVM选项，如果最大元空间大小为
not used then the JVM is you know free
不使用JVM，您知道免费吗
to use all of the native memory
使用所有本机内存
available to it because the meta space
可用，因为元空间
unlike permanent generation is allocated
与分配永久代不同
from native memory alright so we talked
来自本机内存，所以我们谈到了
about out of memory error or memory leak
关于内存不足错误或内存泄漏
situation with meta space and what what
元空间的情况以及什么
is this
这是
you know another space compressed class
你知道另一个空间压缩类
space so compressed class space is
空间，所以压缩的类空间是
actually part of meta space which is a
实际上是元空间的一部分
you know logical region
你知道逻辑区域
it's not physically part of meta space
它实际上不是元空间的一部分
it's a logical it's a region which is
这是合乎逻辑的，这是一个区域
logically included into the meta space
逻辑上包含在元空间中
and we have meta space you know meta
我们有元空间，你知道元
space having compressed class space if
具有压缩类空间的空间，如果
the option use compressed class pointers
该选项使用压缩的类指针
is enabled which is enabled if use
已启用，如果使用则启用
compressed oops is enable and which is
压缩oops已启用，这是
true for 64-bit platforms so by default
对于64位平台为true，因此默认情况下
you would have used compressed class
你会用压缩类
pointers on on your 64-bit JVM and with
和您的64位JVM上的指针
this option on this the 64-bit class
在64位类上的此选项
pointers are represented by 32-bit
指针由32位表示
offset so there is a you know separate
抵消，所以有一个你知道分开
space a separate memory pool and the
分配一个单独的内存池，
class metadata in that memory pool can
该内存池中的类元数据可以
be referenced by 32-bit offsets instead
被32位偏移量代替
of 64-bit pointers by default 1gb of
默认情况下64位指针的1gb
address space is reserved for the
地址空间为
compressed class space when you know the
当您知道压缩的类空间时
JVM initializes and but this can be
JVM初始化，但这可以是
configured using option compressed class
使用选项压缩类配置
space size and an important point here
空间大小和这里的重点
is that the the the option max meta
是选项最大元
space size sets an upper limit on on the
空间大小为
committed sizes of both these spaces
这两个空间的承诺大小
meta space and compressed class space so
元空间和压缩类空间
to understand this better if we don't
如果我们不了解的话会更好
have compressed class pointers enable in
启用了压缩的类指针
the Java heap we have you know objects
我们让您知道对象的Java堆
in objects we have these class pointers
在对象中，我们有这些类指针
so these class pointers on 64-bit
所以这些类指针在64位上
platforms are 64-bit 64-bit platforms
平台是64位64位平台
our 64-bit pointers and these 64-bit
我们的64位指针和这些64位
pointers are then used to reference to
然后使用指针来引用
class metadata in meta space but when we
在元空间中对元数据进行分类，但是当我们
have used compressed class pointers
使用了压缩的类指针
enabled these underscore class pointers
启用这些下划线类指针
in Java objects in the Java heap are
Java堆中的Java对象是
actually 32 bit offset so it says you
实际上是32位偏移，所以它说您
know space in our Java heaps if we have
知道我们Java堆中的空间（如果有）
32-bit pointers instead of 64-bit so
32位指针而不是64位指针
these 32-bit offsets can be used to
这些32位偏移量可用于
reference to this class metadata in
引用此类中的元数据
pressed glass space and when we have
压玻璃空间，当我们有
used compressed glass pointers on and if
使用了压缩玻璃指针，如果
we look at the GC log entry we can see
我们看一下GC日志条目
that there are you know two lines one
你知道两行
for marrow space and the another one is
骨髓空间，另一个是
for compressed class space and note here
用于压缩的课堂空间，请在此处注意
that you know the committed size of meta
您知道meta的承诺大小
space is 4 8 6 4 K which includes the
空间是4 8 6 4 K，其中包括
committed size of compressed class space
压缩类空间的已承诺大小
so 512 K is not you know a separate
所以512 K不是一个单独的
space it is included in 4 8 6 4 k for
它包含在4 8 6 4 k中的空间
meta space diagnostic data collection
元空间诊断数据收集
and analysis for permanent generation
和分析，用于永久生成
and meta space so we should be
和元空间，所以我们应该
collecting GC logs and those can be
收集GC日志，这些可以是
collected with verbose class or trace
用详细的类或跟踪收集
class loading trace class unloading
类加载跟踪类卸载
options we can collect it we should be
我们可以收集的选项，我们应该
collecting data with J map - pom stat
用J map收集数据-pom stat
for JDK is up to JDK 7 and J map - CL
用于JDK的版本取决于JDK 7和J映射-CL
start for JDK 8 onwards and he prompts
从JDK 8开始，他提示
help in diagnosing or investigating
帮助诊断或调查
permanent generation on meta space
元空间上的永久生成
related issues as well and JDK 8 onwards
相关问题以及JDK 8及更高版本
class statistics information can be
班级统计信息可以是
collected with J command GC dot class
用J命令GC点类收集
underscore stats command so you know
下划线stats命令，以便您知道
while investigating the classes or class
在调查班级或班级时
loader related memory problems we should
加载程序相关的内存问题，我们应该
we need to make sure that the classes
我们需要确保课程
are getting unloaded make sure we you
正在卸货，请确保我们您
know there the option - X no class GC is
知道那里的选项-X没有类GC
not in use if it is there your classes
如果您的课程在那里，请不要使用
will not get unloaded
不会被卸载
you know the JVM would keep loading
你知道JVM会继续加载
classes and none of the classes get
类，没有一个类得到
unloaded you will bloat the the meta
卸载后，您会at肿元数据
space or permanent generation usage and
空间或永久性发电用途以及
ensure that CMS class unloading enabled
确保启用CMS类卸载
option is on when using CMS on Java 6 or
在Java 6或更高版本上使用CMS时，此选项打开
Java 7 -
Java 7-
sure that classes are getting unloaded
确保正在卸载类
during concurrent marking cycles
在并发标记周期中
otherwise they get unloaded only at full
否则，它们只能全部卸载
GCS so here this is the logs collected
GCS，所以这是收集的日志
with - for both class and these logs are
与-对于类和这些日志都是
important to tell us
告诉我们很重要
you know if the classes are getting
你知道上课了吗
loaded from correct package or jar files
从正确的软件包或jar文件加载
and if they are getting unloaded when we
如果他们在我们卸货的时候
expect them to so in this specific GC
期望他们在这个特定的GC中如此
logs entry we can see that there is a
日志条目，我们可以看到有一个
full GC and it is happening because meta
完整的GC，它之所以发生是因为meta
space has reached is high-water mark and
空间已达到高水位线，
here we can see that you know there is
在这里我们可以看到你知道有
enough room available in meta space meta
meta空间中有足够的可用空间meta
space capacities at 6 GB but its usage
空间容量为6 GB，但使用率
is only at 4 GB and it is still you know
只有4 GB，仍然是您知道的
throwing out of memory error if you look
如果您看，抛出内存不足错误
closely the out of memory error being
接近内存不足错误
thrown is for compressed class space not
抛出是为了压缩类空间而不是
for meta space so that that you know
元空间，以便您知道
separate region we talked about in
我们讨论过的另一个地区
previous slides the compressed class
上一张幻灯片的压缩类
space which is part of meta space
作为元空间一部分的空间
doesn't have enough room to load more
没有足够的空间来加载更多
classes so we should be using you know
类，所以我们应该使用您知道的
compressed class space size option to
压缩类空间大小选项
configure the size for compressed class
配置压缩类的大小
space we can see class loader statistics
我们可以看到类加载器统计信息的空间
collected with the palm stat the JDK is
随手掌收集到的JDK是
you know up to JDK 7 which have a
您知道多达JDK 7的
permanent generation and JDK 8 onwards
永久一代和JDK 8起
we can use J map there are CL stats
我们可以使用J map有CL统计
option to collect class loader stressed
选择收集类加载器的选项压力很大
statistics so class loader statistics is
统计信息，因此类加载器统计信息是
important because it gives us
重要，因为它给了我们
information about the class loader
有关类加载器的信息
instances available and the classes
可用实例和类
loaded by them whether these classes
他们是否加载了这些类
class loaders are alive or dead in
装载机是活着的还是死的
memory or you know the the number of
记忆或你知道的数量
classes loaded by them or the bytes
它们加载的类或字节
occupied by those classes in Metis P
在Metis P中被那些班级占用
permanent generation so heap dumps help
永久生成，因此堆转储帮助
in this case as well we should be
在这种情况下，我们也应该
looking for classes that should have
寻找应该有的课程
been unloaded and eclipse matt has a
被卸载，日食哑光有一个
very nice feature called duplicate
非常好的功能，称为重复
classes which can show us the duplicate
可以向我们显示重复项的类
classes which have been loaded you know
你知道已经加载的类
by multiple instances of class loaders
通过类加载器的多个实例
here in this case you know this example
在这种情况下，你知道这个例子
shows duplicate classes and here we can
显示重复的类，在这里我们可以
see that the jacks be generated classes
看到千斤顶被生成类
there are multiple instances of those
有那些的多个实例
classes which are loaded by different
由不同的类加载
class loader instances and in this case
类加载器实例，在这种情况下
the issue was you know we had the the
问题是您知道我们有
customer who reported this issue they
报告此问题的客户
had different version of Jack's B
有不同版本的杰克B
libraries on their class path and which
类路径上的库以及
was causing class linking errors and
导致类链接错误，并且
that that led to loading of multiple
导致加载多个
classes by different class loaders so
类由不同的类加载器
you know duplicate classes can give us
你知道重复的课可以给我们
clues where we should be looking for why
我们应该在哪里寻找线索
these classes are getting you know
这些课让你知道
loaded multiple number of times so out
加载了多次，所以
of memory error due to finalization so
由于完成而导致的内存错误
as we all know finalization is a feature
众所周知，终结是一个功能
in Java where your class can have a
在Java中，您的班级可以有一个
finalized method and instruct JVM that
确定方法并指示JVM
you know don't collect my objects until
你知道不要收集我的东西直到
my finalized method has been executed so
我的最终方法已执行，因此
even if you're even if the objects of
即使你是
offers in a specific class which has a
具有特定类别的优惠
finalized method are eligible for
最终方法有资格
collection they won't be collected until
直到他们才会被收集
finalizer thread has the has the chance
终结器线程有机会
to to execute finalized method on those
对那些执行最终方法
instances so we have the single only
实例，所以我们只有一个
thread finalizer thread which you know
您知道的线程终结器线程
has the responsibility to to execute
有执行的责任
finalized method on objects which are
最终确定对象的方法
pending finalization and if this single
待定案，如果这单
thread is not able to keep up with the
线程无法跟上
width
宽度
Lord that has been added to its queue
已添加到队列中的主
you know if it lags behind then we will
你知道如果它落后了，那么我们会
have you know a list of objects which
你知道物体清单吗
are otherwise garbage and if if they
否则是垃圾，如果他们
were collected we would have room
被收集，我们将有空间
available in Java heap or you know
在Java堆中可用，或者您知道
corresponding room in native memory but
本机内存中的相应空间，但是
they are still there because their
他们仍然在那里，因为他们
finalize method needs to be executed so
finalize方法需要执行，因此
this this could waste a lot of memory
这可能会浪费很多内存
and good news is that finalization has
好消息是定稿有
been deprecated in Java 9 and this is
在Java 9中已弃用，这是
the CR ID for that change which you know
您知道的更改的CR ID
with which it has been deprecated in
已不推荐使用
Java 9 and this bug report actually
Java 9和此错误报告实际上
talks about alternative solutions which
谈论替代解决方案
should be used rather than using
应该使用而不是使用
finalization so which diagnostic data
最终确定哪些诊断数据
and tools can help us we can see objects
工具可以帮助我们看到物体
pending finalization using j console
使用J Console进行挂起的终结处理
using j map - finalizar info and we can
使用j map-finalizar信息，我们可以
see you know information about finalized
看到您知道有关定稿的信息
the objects pending finalization using
待完成的对象使用
heap dumps as well so here in J console
堆转储也是如此，因此在J控制台中
we can see that you know pending
我们可以看到您知道未决
finalization objects the count is 0 here
最终确定对象的计数为0
but if this count is high this means
但是如果这个数字很高，那就意味着
that the objects which are pending
待处理的对象
finalization are wasting our Java heap
最终确定浪费了我们的Java堆
memory and if those objects are holding
内存，以及那些对象是否在保存
something in native memory if they have
如果他们有本机内存中的某些内容
allocated buffers in native memory then
然后在本机内存中分配缓冲区
those resources are also being held on
这些资源也被保留
because of the objects pending
因为有待处理的对象
finalization we can see information
最终确定，我们可以看到信息
about finalized errs in eclipse matte as
关于月食遮罩的最终错误
well
好
by analyzing heap dumps so code cache is
通过分析堆转储，以便代码缓存是
full and compiler has been disabled so
已满，编译器已被禁用，因此
there is a separate memory pool in the
有一个单独的内存池
JVM which which stores the compiled code
存储已编译代码的JVM
generated by JIT compilers and this
由JIT编译器生成的
memory pool you know has a defined size
您知道的内存池具有定义的大小
specified size and that it can also get
指定的大小，它也可以得到
full and when
充满和何时
this memory pool becomes full you would
该内存池已满，您会
see this message that the code cache is
看到此消息，代码缓存是
full and compiler has been disabled
已满，编译器已被禁用
though you won't see it's just a warning
虽然您不会看到这只是一个警告
your application won't exit you you
您的申请不会退出您
won't see any out of memory error but
不会看到任何内存不足错误，但是
there are disadvantages you know there
你知道那里有缺点
are performance penalties when when you
是您的性能损失
or when you see this message in your
或者当您在自己的
application run so when when code cache
应用程序运行，以便当代码缓存时
becomes full and emergency code cache
变满，紧急代码缓存
cleanup is invoked which actually
清理实际上被调用
discards almost half of the compiled
丢弃几乎一半的已编译
code and if that compile code is
代码，如果该编译代码是
required soon after you know soon it is
很快知道就需要
discarded then the compiler has to work
丢弃然后编译器必须工作
again to compile those methods so you
再次编译这些方法，以便您
would have performance degradation
会降低性能
because your your compile code is gone
因为您的编译代码不见了
though that compiled those methods will
虽然编译这些方法会
run an interpreted mode now and the
现在运行解释模式，
compiler will take resources to
编译器将占用资源
recompile those methods so the we should
重新编译这些方法，所以我们应该
make efforts to avoid this situation and
努力避免这种情况，并
we should ensure that the code cache
我们应该确保代码缓存
size is sufficient enough to hold our
大小足以容纳我们的
compiled code and there is an option
编译的代码，有一个选择
reserved code cache size using which we
保留的代码缓存大小
can configure our code cache size so out
可以配置我们的代码缓存大小
of memory error for native memory so
本机内存的内存错误，因此
these two examples show that JVM is
这两个例子表明JVM是
running out of native memory so when we
用完本机内存，所以当我们
when we see this error message this
当我们看到此错误消息时
means that JVM is not able to allocate
表示JVM无法分配
from native memory which is not managed
从不受管理的本机内存中
by the JVM not directly managed by the
由JVM而不直接由JVM管理
JVM so this process our current process
JVM，所以这个过程就是我们当前的过程
or other processes on the system might
或系统上的其他进程可能
be consuming native memory and we can
消耗本机内存，我们可以
make more room for you know native
让更多的空间让您知道本地人
memory by reducing the Java heap size
通过减少Java堆大小来增加内存
are reducing the permanent generation or
正在减少永久世代或
meta space size reducing the number of
元空间大小减少了
active threads are there stack sizes are
活动线程在那里有堆栈大小
reducing by terminating some of the
通过终止一些减少
processes on our system which we don't
我们系统上没有的流程
need at that moment and if the above
当时需要，如果以上
doesn't help we might be facing a native
对我们可能面对的本地人没有帮助
memory leak for example you know j'ni
例如内存泄漏，你知道j'ni
code might be j'ni or JVM ti coal might
代码可能是j'ni或JVM Ti Coal
be allocating native buffers and might
分配本机缓冲区，并可能
not be D allocating them as necessary
不必D根据需要分配它们
so which diagnostic data can help us to
因此哪些诊断数据可以帮助我们
troubleshoot native memory issues native
解决本机内存问题
memory leaks you know two kinds of
内存泄漏你知道两种
native memory leaks it could be in the
本机内存泄漏可能在
JVM or it could be outside JVM you know
JVM或它可能在JVM之外
some code outside JVM might be might be
JVM之外的一些代码可能是
leaking native memory so for tracking
泄漏本机内存，以便进行跟踪
native memory leaks in the JVM we have a
JVM中的本机内存泄漏
tool called native memory tracker we
我们称为本机内存跟踪器的工具
should use this tool to to understand
应该使用这个工具来了解
the usage of native memory by by the JVM
JVM对本机内存的使用
or we could use you know for for
或者我们可以用你知道的
tracking native memory leaks outside JVM
跟踪JVM外的本机内存泄漏
we need to you know rely on platform
我们需要您知道依靠平台
native OS level tools for example pea
本机操作系统级别的工具，例如豌豆
map to look at the process map to
映射以查看流程图
understand where you know which parts of
了解您知道哪里的哪个部分
the memory is consumed by you know which
您知道哪个消耗了内存
allocations and results from native
来自本地的分配和结果
memory leaks tools leak tools such as
内存泄漏工具泄漏工具，例如
Libya mam valgrind etc and of course
利比亚mam valgrind等，当然
inspecting different segments of the
检查不同部分
core file can also reveal information
核心文件还可以显示信息
about where what kind of native memory
关于什么样的本机内存
allocations are causing Nitin and the
分配造成了Nitin和
the observed native out of memory error
观察到的本机内存不足错误
we can use a native memory - tracker
我们可以使用本机内存-跟踪器
tool as I said to track native memory
我所说的跟踪本机内存的工具
allocations which are done by the JVM
由JVM完成的分配
and it cannot track memory allocated
并且它无法跟踪分配的内存
outside the JVM or by native libraries
JVM外部或本地库
so to use nmt we can use option native
所以要使用nmt，我们可以使用本机选项
memory tracking and we need to you know
内存跟踪，我们需要您知道
launch our applications with this option
使用此选项启动我们的应用程序
on and
在和
this option can be used at two levels
此选项可以在两个级别上使用
somebody and detail depending upon the
某人和细节取决于
verbosity level of information we would
信息的详细程度
like to see and then we can use J
喜欢看，然后我们可以使用J
command to connect to the process and
命令连接到进程
extract native memory in usage
提取使用中的本机内存
information using VM dot native
使用VM dot native的信息
underscore memory command this is how
下划线内存命令这是
the output from VM dot native underscore
VM点本机下划线的输出
memory looks like this shows you know
内存看起来像这样，您知道
the memory used internally by the JVM by
JVM内部使用的内存，由
different components of the JVM by you
JVM的不同组件
know Java heap threads compiler GC so
知道Java堆线程编译器GC这样
this gives us a clue you know which
这为我们提供了一个线索，您知道
which part of the JVM is consuming more
JVM的哪个部分消耗更多
memory or is you know growing in usage
内存还是您知道使用率在增长
of memory and we can collect a baseline
内存，我们可以收集基线
output using nmt and that baseline can
使用nmt输出，该基线可以
be compared against you know outputs
与您知道的输出进行比较
collected at different stages of
在不同阶段收集
application run and see which parts are
应用程序运行并查看哪些部分
growing in memory usage so for native
内存使用量的增长，因此对于本机
memory leaks outside JVM we need to use
我们需要使用的JVM外部内存泄漏
a native platform native memory leak
本机平台本机内存泄漏
detection tools for example we can use
例如我们可以使用的检测工具
dbx laboum m valgrind purify and so on
dbx laboum m valgrind纯化等
so to summarize causes of memory related
所以总结一下与记忆有关的原因
problems could be you know miss
问题可能是你知道小姐
configuration of memory pools excessive
内存池配置过多
use of finalized errs like explicit GC
使用最终错误，例如显式GC
invocations or memory leaks and we the
调用或内存泄漏，我们
first step to understand or to
第一步了解或
troubleshoot memory related problems is
解决与内存相关的问题是
to size our memory pools appropriately
适当地调整我们的内存池大小
and the tools that we can use to
以及我们可以用来
troubleshoot memory problems are heap
解决内存问题是堆
dump on out of memory error and print
转储出内存错误并打印
class histogram options J console J
类直方图选项J控制台J
command J map GC logs Eclipse mat and MT
命令J map GC记录Eclipse mat和MT
are native memory detection tools
是本机内存检测工具
so these are some references you can you
这些是您可以参考的
know look at refer to troubleshooting
知道看参考故障排除
guides here I provided links for JDK 9
此处的指南我提供了JDK 9的链接
and JDK 8 troubleshooting guides I have
和我拥有的JDK 8故障排除指南
a blog where i share my troubleshooting
我分享我的疑难解答的博客
experiences you know quite often and
你经常知道的经历
there is a free ongoing online course
正在进行免费的在线课程
for troubleshooting memory issues in
用于解决内存中的问题
java applications the enrollments are
注册的Java应用程序是
still open until october 11 so you could
仍然开放到10月11日，所以您可以
enroll into that course and you know
报名参加那门课程，你知道
learn more about how to troubleshoot
详细了解如何进行故障排除
memory issues and there's an article on
内存问题，有一篇关于
troubleshooting Java memory issues on
对Java内存问题进行故障排除
info cube the link is given here so
信息立方体链接在这里给出，所以
that's all I had to share thank you
这就是我要分享的全部，谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]